# Krishna Jangir

Having experience in front end technologies. Skilled in java script frameworks like ionic and angular. Having knowledge in Html, Css, Git, Json, ES6 and Typescript. Strong professional with Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science from Sobhasaria Engineering College(Sikar).



	lesis booi	:00@	mail.com
$\mathbf{I}$	KHSHHAI	199(WC	IIIIail.COIII

Gurgaon, India

in linkedin.com/in/krishna-jangir-997167158

### +91 80949-15483

15 June, 1996

github.com/Krishnajangir

Bootstrap, Angular Material, Prime

Interaction with new people

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

### Senior Engineer

Nagarro

06/2022 - Present Gurgaon

## **Associate Technology**

Publicis sapient

03/2021 - 06/2022 Gurgaon

# Associate Consultant - Frontend

Oodles technologies Private LMT.

10/2019 - 03/2021 Gurgaon

# Firebase database

Node Js, React JS

INTERESTS

LANGUAGES

Full Professional Proficiency

Singing

English

# SKILLS

Angular JavaScript, Typescript

Html, CSS, Git

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

## **PROJECTS**

#### Verizon (03/2021 - Present)

- Designing, implementing application with different technologies.
- Code management using github and jira.
- Management with agile scrum and followed all the rules of agile software development.
- We are working on angular 8 version and my responsibility is to enhance site's performance.

### Bhaasha (10/2019 - 03/2021)

- Designing, implementing application with different technologies.
- Code management using GitHub and bitbucket, Code review and implementation.
- Created build for apple store and play store for the hybrid applications.
- migrated the same in angular 9.

# **TRAINING** This project was based on angular JS and ionic 1. And we also

Industrial Training (23 May 2017-07 July 2017) Ducat Institute(Gurgaon)

Hindi

# **EDUCATION**

#### **B.tech**

Sobhasaria Engineering College, Sikar

08/2014 - 06/2018

Senior Secondary Sanskar Sr Sec School, Sikar 82.91%